And President Trump decided to use the
bunker buster bombs against the Iranian
nuclear site just so that the Israelis
would not use nuclear weapons against
Iran.
Uh I have some friends in the CIA, in
the Defense Department, and in the White
House. I was talking to them recently
about the situation between Israel and
Iran. One thing that many Americans
don't understand is that the Israelis
really see Iran as an existential
threat. And the Israelis believe that
the Americans don't understand
how threatened the Israelis feel. With
that said, literally every
American president who has entertained
an Israeli foreign minister since the
1980s, since Ronald Reagan was
president, has had to deal with Israeli
requests to bomb Iran. Every single
Israeli prime minister that visits
Washington says, "We want you to bomb
Iran." And every American president has
said, "No, I'm not going to bomb Iran."
until this president. Now, my friends
inside the White House and in the CIA
tell me that the reason why President
Trump decided to change that policy and
decided to bomb Iran uh bomb Iran was
because this time
Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin
Netanyahu said that the Israelis were so
sure that the Iranians were planning a
nuclear attack on Israel that the
Israelis were prepared to use nuclear
weapons against Iran. And President
Trump decided to use the bunker buster
bombs against the Iranian nuclear site
just so that the Israelis would not use
nuclear weapons against Iran. I don't
think that either the Israeli or the
American attacks had any lasting effect
on the Iranian nuclear program at all.
The Iranians would never be so foolish
as to have all of their eggs in one
basket. There are facilities spread all
over the country, most of them deep
underground where these experiments uh
are taking place. And while the
Americans can bomb one deep site and the
Israelis can bomb other sites that are
not as deep, the work continues because
there are so many different sites. So,
you know, of course, to save face, the
United States and Israel are going to
have to say that the bombings were
successful. Uh I I don't believe that
they were. And in fact, just judging by
the Iranian response where the the
Iranians essentially shrugged their
shoulders and said, "Okay, you've bombed
us. Now, we're going to move on." That
tells me that these bombings were not
terribly successful.